http://flexcoat.com/privacy-policy

Menu
FREE SHIPPING on all orders over $49 (Continental US Only)
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any
Change/correct any data we have about you
Have us delete any data we have about you
Express concern you have about our use of your data
Website Links
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Online Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, mailing list or informational pamphlet) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Using Flex Coat FinishInstructional Video on MixingMeasuring and MixingRod Wrapping Finish TipsRod Building ResourcesCustom Fitting Reel Seat ArborsAttaching Guides with AdhesiveHelpful DocumentsInstructional VideosFlex Coat Variable Speed DC Motors for Custom Rod BuildingFlex Coat Dual Control Rod Wrapping and Finishing MotorFlex Coat Rod Building – Finish Application Wave TechniqueFlex Coat DC777 Power Wrapper and FinisherFlex Coat Variable Speed DC Motors for Custom Rod BuildingInstalling a Pre-shaped Cork Casting GripFlex Coat Lure DrumWorking with Lure Epoxy Gel Coat and Iridescent CrystalsApplying Flex Coat Rod Wrapping FinishSelf Adjusting Chuck & Slip ClutchTying a Locking Wrap on Micro GuidesTools, Tips, & TricksFlex Coat Final Coat on Big Offshore Rods featuring Pat BrianMaking a Split GripMaking a Fighting ButtMaking a Recessed Hood on a Fly Rod GripMixing and Applying Epoxy GluesInstalling a Tip TopMastering Guide Foot AdhesiveCork Lathe Tips and TricksWriting on RodsBuilding a Pre-Shaped Cork HandleMaking a Power ReamerInstructional Video on Mixing
Have questions? Contact us to find out more about our products, receive support on an existing product, and to get answers to your questions.
Get In Touch
©2020 Flex Coat | All Rights Reserved | Privacy Policy | Legal | Branded With Kulture Digital
